<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"

xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
>

<channel>
	<title>Beebom</title>
	<atom:link href="https://beebom.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://beebom.com</link>
	<description>Tech that matters</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:58:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.10</generator>
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">129268571</site>	<item>
		<title>25 Best Horror Movies on Netflix You Should Watch</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/best-horror-movies-on-netflix/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/best-horror-movies-on-netflix/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Beebom Staff]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netflix]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186010</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Best Horror Movies on Netflix 2019" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>Netflix is a great streaming service and we love it for its selection of movies, series, and originals. The streaming service provides many genres of movies including comedy, romantic, thrillers etc. I myself am a fan of Netflix&#8217;s horror movie collection and that&#8217;s why we bring you the best horror movies streaming on Netflix right [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Best Horror Movies on Netflix 2019" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Best-Horror-Movies-on-Netflix-2019-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>Netflix is a great streaming service and we love it for its selection of movies, series, and originals. The streaming service provides many genres of movies including <a href="https://beebom.com/best-comedy-movies-on-netflix/" >comedy</a>, romantic, thrillers etc. I myself am a fan of Netflix&#8217;s horror movie collection and that&#8217;s why we bring you the best horror movies streaming on Netflix right now. We have carefully chosen the 25 best horror movies on Netflix to watch in 2019. So far, Netflix has added a number of scary movies which look absolutely terrifying and we can&#8217;t wait to watch it. So without any delay, let&#8217;s jump to the list and find the best horror movies streaming on Netflix.
<p><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Note:</strong></span> All of the mentioned movies are available in the US. However, if you are based out of another country, click on the movie links provided below to check the availability.</em>
<h2>The Best Scary Movies on Netflix in 2019</h2>
<p>Here, we have sorted the 25 best scary movies available on Netflix right now. We have included many of the sub-genres like classic horrors, psychological thrillers, zombie horror, cannibal horror, horror films based on books, and more. You can go through the list and pick any of them and watch it. I am sure you won&#8217;t be disappointed. So having said that, let&#8217;s get to the list.
<p><em><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Note:</strong></span> The Rotten Tomatoes ratings are shown in the Expert / Audience format.</em>
<h2>List of Best Horror Movies on Netflix</h2>
<h2>1. Get Out (2017)</h2>
<p>Get Out is a horror flick about an African-American man who falls in love with a Caucasian woman. <strong>The movie is seemingly normal in the beginning, but the horrors are waiting</strong> as the film progresses. The movie gets even more disturbing with further discoveries of truth. At the outset, Get Out is brilliant at its depiction of race and psychological problems. You should watch this movie for its spellbinding story.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/DzfpyUB60YY?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7.7</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 98% / 86%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80149258" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Get Out on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>2. The Shining (1980)</h2>
<p>The Shining is a psychological horror film about a man dealing with his past trauma. To get away from all the unnerving feelings, the main character which is played by Jack Nicholson moves to a countryside hotel with his family. But <strong>living away from the city, he starts to lose his sanity</strong>. The movie is a terrifying experience and feels much more real. You should watch this Stanley Kubrick classic for its epic climax. To sum up, The Shining is one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should not miss it at all.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/5Cb3ik6zP2I?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 8.4</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 86% / 93%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/959008" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Shining on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>3. The Sixth Sense (1999)</h2>
<p>The Sixth Sense is a chilling psychological thriller about a child possessed by an evil spirit and a psychologist trying to save the child. The story revolves around the two characters and it gets amply terrifying with each passing moment. <strong>The intersection of psychology and dark spirits make for an unsettling experience</strong>. I would highly recommend watching this old classic, The Sixth Sense.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/VG9AGf66tXM?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 8.1</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 86% / 90%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/26797528" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Sixth Sense on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>4. The Conjuring (2013)</h2>
<p>The Conjuring is a supernatural horror film which revolves around a family and two paranormal investigators. The family has moved to a new house, but<strong> the unusual activity at night has made them wary for their children</strong>. To free the house from dark forces, the investigators are called upon, but then the story takes a suspenseful turn. The Conjuring is absolutely gripping and you would be terrified at many instances. If you are new to horror movies, The Conjuring is the gold standard to begin with.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/k10ETZ41q5o?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7.5</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 85% / 83%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/70251894" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Conjuring on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>5. Train to Busan (2016)</h2>
<p>Train to Busan remains <strong>a classic movie among all the zombie movies</strong>. And the great part is that it&#8217;s available on Netflix. The movie is about a father and his daughter who are on a train to South Korea. The film turns really horrid when a zombie outbreak is reported in parts of South Korea. To survive the zombies, the father-daughter takes on the frightful zombies face to face. The movie is simply terrifying, to say the least. If you like the zombie genre of movies, Train to Busan is to watch for. It&#8217;s simply one of the best horror movies on Netflix right now.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/pyWuHv2-Abk?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7.5</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 95% / 88%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80117824" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Train to Busan on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>6. It (2017)</h2>
<p>It is a horror-thriller movie which is based on Stephen King&#8217;s novel of the same name. The book was a huge success and so was the movie. The film is about a forgotten evil clown named Pennywise who returns to a town named Derry to spread terror. <strong>The movie takes a terrifying turn when a group of young kids faces the clown</strong>. It is truly a masterpiece among the horror movies and you should definitely watch it. To sum up, if you want to seethe in fear, It is one of the best horror movies on Netflix.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/hAUTdjf9rko?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7.4</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 85% / 84%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80130987" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out It on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>7. The Wailing (2016)</h2>
<p>The Wailing is a horror film set in a rural village of South Korea. It&#8217;s about a <strong>policeman who investigates a series of mysterious murders</strong> in the village. As the days pass by, the policeman is confronted with bizarre trails and unusual suspects. It&#8217;s one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should watch it for the story. Also, I strongly recommend this movie for the insane climax.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/43uAputjI4k?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7.4</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 99% / 81%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80108974" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Wailing on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>8. Raw (2016)</h2>
<p>Raw is a Belgian horror film about a vegetarian student who goes to a veterinary school to learn the techniques of animal treatment. For the first time, the student tastes raw meat and from there, <strong>the movie turns into a cannibal nightmare</strong>. The film is pretty fast-paced and you would find enough scary scenes which might make you quit the movie. But if you trudge along, Raw can make you feel the real terror at its finest. Also if you like Cannibal movies, Raw is a must-watch.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/gFlXVX2af_Y?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 7</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 92% / 76%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80115405" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Raw on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>9. Insidious (2013)</h2>
<p>Insidious is a horror film about a couple and their struggle to save their son from dark forces. <strong>The movie revolves around the familiar trope of a haunted house</strong> and the fight to wade off the evil spirit. The movie is written by the writers of classic horror, Paranormal Activity so there are great sequences which would put you on the edge. Also, the mixture of rituals and satanic verses makes for a frightful experience. Definitely watch Insidious for the classic haunted house story.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/fBbi4NeebAk?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.9</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 66% / 62%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/70142542" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Insidious on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>10. Under The Shadow (2016)</h2>
<p>Under the Shadow is a horror flick set during the 1980s war in the Middle East. The movie is in the Persian language and has won many international awards in the foreign-language category. <strong>A mother in a war-ravaged country tries to protect her daughter</strong> from supernatural forces. In order to free her daughter from evil possession, the mother faces the demons. The movie is absolutely great on visuals and you will be aghast by the storytelling. Simply put, Under the Shadow is one of the best horror movies on Netflix. You should defintely watch it.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/kHVFP80Upxw?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;start=29&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.9</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 99% / 74%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80096786" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Under The Shadow on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>11. The Witch (2015)</h2>
<p>The Witch is the most terrifying yet beautifully shot horror film set in England in the year 1630. <strong>The movie is about a farmer&#8217;s family where their son disappears one evening</strong>. After that, the crop starts failing, and the sister gets possessed by an evil spirit and a series of unpleasant things start to happen in the village. The Witch is a great story of Witchcraft, black magic, and the triumph of the good. It&#8217;s one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should definitely watch it.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/iQXmlf3Sefg?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.8</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 90% / 58%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80037280" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Witch on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>12. The Autopsy of Jane Doe (2016)</h2>
<p>The Autopsy of Jane Doe is a supernatural horror film about the father-son duo who does the autopsy of Jane Doe and finds some bizarre clues. <strong>The revelation of autopsy is frightening and takes the story to a whole another level</strong>. It is really the most horrifying movie pulled in such a great way. It doesn&#8217;t follow the horror movie trope and still shines throughout the movie. The Autopsy of Jane Doe is one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should not miss it.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/mtTAhXuiRTc?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.8</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 86% / 70%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80022613" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Autopsy of Jane Doe on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>13. The Invitation (2015)</h2>
<p>The Invitation is a psychological thriller which is based on the failed marriage of a couple. The woman calls her ex-husband to a dinner party where he shows up with his new girlfriend. <strong>After a while, a violent drama ensues with the trauma of the past</strong>. There are some unsettling scenes where the characters are unable to distinguish their paranoia with reality. The movie is unusual at best and sometimes, mindbending. If you like this kind of horror movie, The Invitation is for you.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/0-mp77SZ_0M?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.7</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 88% / 70%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80048977" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Invitation on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>14. Gerald&#8217;s Game (2017)</h2>
<p>Gerald&#8217;s Game is a horror movie based on Stephen King&#8217;s novel of the same name. <strong>The film is about a couple who want to rekindle their sex life after marriage</strong>. They move to an isolated farmhouse where an accident happens and the story takes a frightful turn. Slowly, the movie builds up the pace and you would be truly terrified on many occasions. Do watch Gerald&#8217;s Game because of the unusual storyline. Also, it&#8217;s one of the best horror movies on Netflix available right now.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/twbGU2CqqQU?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.6</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 90% / 72%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80128722" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Gerald&#8217;s Game on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>15. Bird Box (2018)</h2>
<p>Bird Box is more of a thriller rather than a horror flick. However, you will surely get the chills throughout the movie. It&#8217;s about a woman, who is played by Sandra Bullock, tries to save her children from an unknown evil entity. What is known though is that <strong>the unknown entity can make you kill yourself if you come face to face</strong> with the supernatural power. The story is quite thrilling and you would be on the edge of your seat for sure.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/INJ2bPFy108?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.6</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 63% / 58%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80196789" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Bird Box on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>16. Hush (2016)</h2>
<p>Hush is an enthralling horror flick about a deaf woman writer living in deep woods away from society. The movie takes a surprising turn when a masked man knocks the door at night. The woman does everything to save herself from the unknown man. <strong>It&#8217;s an absorbing story which takes you through the extreme highs and lows</strong>. Hush brings some great effects and heart pacing story to the audience. You should not miss it.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q_P8WCbhC6s?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.6</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 92% / 73%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80091879" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Hush on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>17. Annabelle (2017)</h2>
<p>Annabelle is a terrifying horror film about a family and a possessed doll. The movie is set in the countryside of America where a couple adopts a child from the local orphanage. <strong>The child brings in her toys and one of them creates havoc</strong> in the entire house. The movie absolutely gets on the nerve and you would be on the edge of your seat during the intense sequences. You should surely watch Annabelle for its beautifully woven story in the hinterland of America. It&#8217;s one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should watch it without any hesitation.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/KisPhy7T__Q?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.5</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 70% / 67%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/in/title/80158661" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Annabelle on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>18. The Devil&#8217;s Candy (2015)</h2>
<p>The Devil Candy is an intense horror film about a painter possessed by satanic forces. <strong>The story is an old movie trope</strong> &#8212; the painter with his family move to a dream house, only to face with a mysterious dark force. The film is highly captivating and keeps you engrossed all through the runtime. The scenes are quite disturbing and you would be gritting your teeth during the intense visuals. It&#8217;s one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should definitely watch it. Not for the faint-hearted.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/rtD3M86ZqDA?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.4</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 92% / 64%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80077861" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Devil&#8217;s Candy on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>19. Apostle (2018)</h2>
<p>Apostle is a British horror film set in London in the year 1905. The movie is about a protagonist who returns to London to meet his sister, only to find out that she is held hostage by a religious cult. <strong>In order to save her, he travels to a mysterious island and the story gets murkier and engrossing</strong>. The story and visuals are really unsettling and you should watch Apostle for that edge of the seat experience. Overall, Apostle is one of the best horror movies on Netflix and you should not miss it.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/J1JdWOqc9Q8?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.3</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 80% / 54%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80158148" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Apostle on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>20. 1922 (2017)</h2>
<p>1922 is a horror drama movie which is based on Stephen King&#8217;s novel of the same name. The movie is <strong>based on a central character who wants to kill her wife</strong> for financial gains. It has lots of twists and turns, finding new ways to keep the audience engaged. The movie turns really enthralling when the father persuades his son to kill his mother. If you like horror movies which can turn the table upside down, 1922 is one of the best horror movies on Netflix to watch.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/3E_fT0aTsjI?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.3</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 88% / 57%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/in/title/80135164" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out 1922 on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>21. The Ritual (2017)</h2>
<p>The Ritual is a British horror movie which revolves around five friends. After the tragic death of one of their friends, they reunite and go for a hike to Sweden. What happens afterward is <strong>a mind-bending tale of horror and mystery</strong>. The Ritual is fantastic with its location, sound effect, and overall setup. If you like the old ways of storytelling, The Ritual is an absolute must-watch. It can slowly seep into your nerves making you scream without measure.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/Vfugwq2uoa0?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.3</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 73% / 59%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80217312" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out The Ritual on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>22. Creep (2014)</h2>
<p>While Creep is not a new movie, it&#8217;s probably one of the realistic horror movies you would find on Netflix. The movie is about an individual who places an online ad requesting for a videographer. A videographer turns to his door, only to find that he wants to film his day creating a sort of video diary. Slowly, <strong>the requests turn absurd and the real-life horror makes it unbelievable to watch</strong>. The mockumentary style film is too real and at the same time horrifying. If you like psychological horror movies, Creep is for you.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/FBR8VcdpE4Y?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.3</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 92% / 65%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/70306646" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Creep on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>23. A Dark Song (2016)</h2>
<p>A Dark Song is a horror <strong>movie about a woman and an occultist where both of them are set out to find the dead</strong>. They move to a distant house to perform a dark ritual. However, what they face after that is even more terrifying. The story is absolutely dark and makes you want to quit the movie. The film is beautifully shot and the background track makes things even more dramatic and suspenseful. You should watch A Dark Song for some great visuals and a compelling story.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/5-S3JqJZJ3s?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe></p>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6.1</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 92% / 60%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80185919" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out A Dark Song on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>24. Cam (2018)</h2>
<p>Cam is a psychological horror film which revolves around an ambitious woman in the world of webcam porn. At the peak of her popularity, <strong>someone replaces her online account with a replica of her</strong>. While she tries to find the person behind the new account, you are taken on an unnerving trip with fear and suspense in equal measure. If you like the new world order of internet fandom with a dash of fear baked in, Cam is the best pick for you.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y9x5ImTWK5s?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 6</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 94% / 56%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80177400" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Cam on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<h2>25. Shelley (2016)</h2>
<p>Shelley is a Danish horror film about a childless couple and their desire to have a child anyhow. <strong>To fulfill their desire, they choose their maid to act as a surrogate</strong>. What happens next will blow your mind as the story takes a surprising turn. The movie is absolutely terrifying with its dark theme, soundtrack, and story. If you love old school movies which can get terrifyingly good, Shelley is a must-watch.
<p><iframe class='youtube-player' type='text/html' width='640' height='360' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/OTc5RSuQkxQ?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;fs=1&#038;autohide=2&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;wmode=transparent' allowfullscreen='true' style='border:0;'></iframe>
<ul>
<li><strong><em>IMDb: 5.2</em></strong></li>
<li><strong><em>Rotten Tomatoes: 100% / 38%</em></strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong><em><a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/80123668" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Check Out Shelley on Netflix</a></em></strong>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>SEE ALSO: <a href="https://beebom.com/best-comedy-movies-on-netflix/" >25 Best Bollywood Movies on Netflix</a></strong>
<h2>Stream The Best Horror Movie on Netflix</h2>
<p>So that was our complete list of 25 best horror movies on Netflix to watch in 2019. We have included all sorts of movies from classic horror to psychological thrillers. You can go ahead and pick any of the movies and you would be in for a terrifying movie experience. Do note that most of the movies are available in the US, but if you are based out of a different country, you can check the availability by clicking on the movie links. So that will be all from us. If you liked our list of horror movies or we missed your favorite classic, do let us know in the comment section below.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/best-horror-movies-on-netflix/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186010</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s a Glimpse at What OxygenOS 10 Based on Android Q May Look Like</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/oxygen-os-10-android-q-first-look/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/oxygen-os-10-android-q-first-look/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kishalaya Kundu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OxygenOS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OxygenOS 10]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186282</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>OnePlus is looking to implement a massive redesign of its OxygenOS ROM, and as always, has been seeking inputs from users and fans around the world. As part of its plans to make the community feel more involved every step of the way, the company recently held a contest to select an honorary Product Manager [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OnePlus-7-Pro-shutterstock-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>OnePlus is looking to implement a massive redesign of its <a href="https://beebom.com/oxygenos-gains-zen-mode-to-help-users-focus-curb-smartphone-addiction/" >OxygenOS ROM</a>, and as always, has been seeking inputs from users and fans around the world. As part of its plans to make the community feel more involved every step of the way, the company recently held a contest to select an honorary Product Manager with a view towards possibly including some of their ideas in the redesigned software.
<p>The winner was a UX designer called Léandro Tijink, who now says that he had the opportunity to present some of his ideas to the OnePlus design team in Shenzhen. He has now posted a series of mock-up screenshots, revealing some of the design changes he suggested at the meeting. While all features and UI elements suggested by Tijink may not make their way to future versions of OxygenOS for a variety of reasons, they do reveal the passion, hard work and thought that he put behind his presentation.
<figure id="attachment_186295" style="width: 640px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-186295" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body1.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="449" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body1.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body1-100x70.jpg 100w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body1-599x420.jpg 599w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Image Courtesy: Léandro Tijink</figcaption></figure>
<p>There are literally dozens more screenshots that show how OxygenOS can be improved with some changes to its UI and added functionalities, with Tijink suggesting several major and minor tweaks over the current official ROM. According to him, the attention to detail with the new features will bring more consistency and <em>&#8216;buttery smooth animations&#8217;</em> to OxygenOS. He actually created a whole new website to post all his images, and you can check them all out by <a href="https://cdn.rovota.com/media/oneplus/pmchallenge-rework/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">clicking here</a>.
<figure id="attachment_186294" style="width: 640px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-186294" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body2.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="450" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body2.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body2-300x211.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body2-100x70.jpg 100w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/OP-OxygenOS-10-mockups-body2-597x420.jpg 597w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Image Courtesy: Léandro Tijink</figcaption></figure>
<p>As can be seen from the screenshots, a whole lot of changes have been suggested to various aspects of the operating system, right from the initial setup process to the launcher, and from the Settings menu to the default Gallery app. With OxygenOS 10 slated to arrive later this year with the OnePlus 7T, it will be interesting to see how many of the proposed changes will be implemented by the company.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/oxygen-os-10-android-q-first-look/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186282</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snapdragon 855 Plus vs Snapdragon 855: What&#8217;s Different?</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/snapdragon-855-plus-vs-snapdragon-855/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/snapdragon-855-plus-vs-snapdragon-855/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 11:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anmol Sachdeva]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ROG Phone 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snapdragon 855]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snapdragon 855 Plus]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=185775</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Snapdragon 855 vs Snapdragon 855 Plus: What&#039;s Different?" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>If you&#8217;ve been keeping up with the latest in the technology world, you would know that Qualcomm surprised us with a mid-cycle refresh of its flagship chipset &#8211; the Snapdragon 855. The upgraded chipset is known as Snapdragon 855 Plus and it brings in tow some changes that make it stand out from the chip [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Snapdragon 855 vs Snapdragon 855 Plus: What&#039;s Different?" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-8-1-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>If you&#8217;ve been keeping up with the latest in the technology world, you would know that Qualcomm surprised us with a mid-cycle refresh of its flagship chipset &#8211; the Snapdragon 855. The upgraded chipset is known as Snapdragon 855 Plus and it brings in tow some changes that make it stand out from the chip maker&#8217;s existing flagship processor.
<p>We already have the first smartphone powered by Snapdragon 855 Plus among us, <a href="https://beebom.com/asus-rog-phone-2-first-impressions/" >the ROG Phone 2</a>, so let&#8217;s check out how the Snapdragon 855 and Snapdragon 855 Plus differ from each other:
<h2>Snapdragon 855 Plus vs Snapdragon 855: Specs</h2>
<p>Before we speak about the upgrades in Snapdragon 855 Plus over the Snapdragon 855 chipset, here&#8217;s a quick look at the specifications of both the chipsets:

<table id="tablepress-872" class="tablepress tablepress-id-872">
<thead>
<tr class="row-1 odd">
	<th class="column-1">&nbsp;</th><th class="column-2"><b>Snapdragon 855</th><th class="column-3"><b>Snapdragon 855 Plus</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody class="row-hover">
<tr class="row-2 even">
	<td class="column-1"><b>CPU Cores</b></td><td class="column-2">octa-core Qualcomm Kryo 485</td><td class="column-3">octa-core Qualcomm Kryo 485</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-3 odd">
	<td class="column-1"><b>CPU Architecture</b></td><td class="column-2">64-bit, 7nm</td><td class="column-3">64-bit, 7nm</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-4 even">
	<td class="column-1"><b>CPU Clock Speed</b></td><td class="column-2">up to 2,84GHz</td><td class="column-3">up tp 2.96GHz</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-5 odd">
	<td class="column-1"><b>GPU</b></td><td class="column-2">Adreno 640, clocked at 585MHz</td><td class="column-3">Adreno 640, clocked at 672MHz</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-6 even">
	<td class="column-1"><b>ISP</b></td><td class="column-2">Spectra 380</td><td class="column-3">Spectra 380</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-7 odd">
	<td class="column-1"><b>Modem</b></td><td class="column-2">Snapdragon X24 LTE</td><td class="column-3">Snapdragon X24 LTE</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-8 even">
	<td class="column-1"><b>Charging</b></td><td class="column-2">Quick Charge 4+</td><td class="column-3">Quick Charge 4+</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<!-- #tablepress-872 from cache -->
<h2>Snapdragon 855 Plus vs Snapdragon 855: Upgrades</h2>
<p>As the comparison table attached above should make it very clear, the <strong>key difference between the two Snapdragon 855 variants is the CPU and GPU</strong> <strong>clock speed</strong>. We can easily call the Snapdragon 855 Plus an <em>overclocked version</em> of the Snapdragon 855 chipset.
<p>The Snapdragon 855 Plus features the same tri-cluster arrangement of the ARM Cortex-A76-based Kryo 485 cores as the original flagship chipset. This includes a prime core, 3 mid-cores, and 4 efficiency cores. This is where the difference between the two chipsets appears as <strong>the prime core of the Snapdragon 855 Plus is clocked at 2.96 GHz</strong> as compared to 2.84GHz. This minor bump in clock speed gives the new flagship chipset a slight edge for handling more graphics-heavy games and apps.
<p>Another notable change between the Snapdragon 855 and Snapdragon 855 Plus is that Adreno 640 GPU on the former is now overclocked to 672MHz as compared to 585MHz clock speed. Qualcomm promises that the said change offers 15% improvement in the gaming performance, which is great for the fledgling gaming phone niche.
<ul>
<li>
<h3>Elite Gaming Features</h3>
</li>
</ul>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186280" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1.jpg" alt="Qualcomm Elite Gaming" width="750" height="500" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/farmto-table-9-1-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" />
<p>Snapdragon 855 Plus also gives Qualcomm the leeway to introduce new Elite Gaming features for smartphones that come equipped with this chipset. They will now support HDR10 rendering for more realistic and smooth gameplay, Q-Sync to help match the display&#8217;s refresh rate to the game&#8217;s frame rate to prevent tearing, and Jank Reducer. Smartphones with this chipset will see reduced janks in a 30FPS gameplay, offering a stutter-free experience with more detailed and crisp graphics rendering.
<p>With the announcement of the Snapdragon 855 Plus, Qualcomm hints that it could be moving to a bi-annual release schedule for its flagship 800-series chipset. This is mere speculation at this point of time, however, it is possible as many premium and flagship Android phones land in the market in the third quarter or later. This mid-cycle chipset refresh could work in the favor of many flagships, especially Google Pixel 4 and Galaxy Note 10 lineups that are set to launch really soon.
<p>However, a more plausible explanation would be that Qualcomm is also jumping on the gaming phone hype train by overclocking its processor to give it that performance boost that gamers might crave for. There isn&#8217;t <em>&#8220;much difference between the</em> <em>two Snapdragon 855 chipsets&#8221;</em> as both are flagship chips that offer a smooth and premium experience.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/snapdragon-855-plus-vs-snapdragon-855/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">185775</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Honor MagicBook Pro With Core i7 CPU, 16GB RAM, 1TB SSD Now Official</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/honor-magicbook-pro-core-launched-specs-pricing-availability/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/honor-magicbook-pro-core-launched-specs-pricing-availability/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 11:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kishalaya Kundu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Honor MagicBook]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Honor MagicBook Pro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huawei]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186247</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>Alongside the Honor 9X series smartphones and the Honor Band 5 fitness tracker, Huawei on Tuesday also launched its premium Honor MagicBook Pro laptop with a super-slim form factor, metal body and narrow bezels. The device features a 16.1-inch full-HD display with 300 nits of brightness and, can be configured with up to 8th-gen Intel [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>Alongside the <a href="https://beebom.com/honor-9x-pro-launched-specs-pricing-availability/" >Honor 9X series</a> smartphones and the <a href="https://beebom.com/honor-band-5-launched-specs-pricing-availability/" >Honor Band 5</a> fitness tracker, Huawei on Tuesday also launched its premium Honor MagicBook Pro laptop with a super-slim form factor, metal body and narrow bezels. The device features a 16.1-inch full-HD display with 300 nits of brightness and, can be configured with up to 8th-gen Intel Core i5-8265U or Core i7-8565U processors, Nvidia GeForce MX250 GPU, 16GB of RAM and 1TB of PCIe SSD storage. It is only 16.9mm thick, weighs 1.7 Kgs and has 4.9mm wide bezels on three sides.
<p>On the software side of things, the ultrabook predictably comes with <a href="https://beebom.com/windows-10-updates/" >Windows 10</a>, but only the <em>Home</em> version and not <em>Pro</em>. Connectivity options include dual-band Wi-Fi, Bluetooth 5.0, 3x USB 3.0 ports and 1x USB Type-C port for charging. Other notable features include a fingerprint sensor under the power button and Dolby Atmos speakers. It also comes with a 1MP front-facing camera and a 56Wh battery that the company says will offer up to 14 hours of local video playback on a single charge.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186261" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-body.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="470" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-body.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-body-300x220.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-body-80x60.jpg 80w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-MagicBook-Pro-body-572x420.jpg 572w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>The Honor MagicBook Pro, which is only being offered in one color for now &#8211; Glacial Silver &#8211; has been priced starting at 5,499 yuan (around Rs. 55,000) for the base model with the aforementioned Core i5 chip, 8GB of RAM and 512GB of storage. The top model with Core i7 CPU + 16GB RAM + 1TB SSD goes up to 7,999 yuan (around Rs. 80,000). Bookings are already open in China, with general availability slated to begin July 29.
<p>Just to recap, Huawei&#8217;s consumer division had a massive day today in China, unveiling a slew of new products, including the Honor 9X and 9X Pro smartphones, the Honor Band 5 fitness tracker and the MagicBook Pro laptop. While the laptop may or may not make its way to India, the phones and the smart band will very likely hit the Indian market sooner rather than later.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/honor-magicbook-pro-core-launched-specs-pricing-availability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186247</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>TikTok User Spend Crossed $10 Million Last Month</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/tiktok-user-spend-crossed-10-million-last-month/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/tiktok-user-spend-crossed-10-million-last-month/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 11:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Akshay Gangwar]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TikTok]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186249</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>If you thought the TikTok craze was dying out, here&#8217;s a reality-check for you. The short video sharing app that has been at the center of a huge number of controversies, is going strong and is growing at an immensely fast rate. According to a report from Sensor Tower, user spending inside the TikTok app [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/TikTok-Ban-Lifted-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>If you thought the TikTok craze was dying out, here&#8217;s a reality-check for you. The short video sharing app that has been at the center of a huge number of controversies, is going strong and is growing at an immensely fast rate.
<p>According to a report from Sensor Tower, user spending inside the TikTok app reached $10 million last month, as compared to $1.6 million in June 2018 — a 588 percent year-over-year growth. Compared to $9 million last month, the app saw a 19% growth in user spend this time around.
<p>Interestingly, according to the Sensor Tower report, while India is the biggest market for TikTok, the highest user spend in the app was from users in China, where the gross revenue for the app has increased 271 percent since January this year.
<p>&#8220;Chinese users accounted for 69 per cent of TikTok&#8217;s in-app revenue last month, up from 30 per cent in June 2018,&#8221; Sensor Tower Founder Oliver Yeh wrote in a blog post on Monday.
<p>&#8220;Last month&#8217;s record spending comes as TikTok is testing several enhancements to its user experience, some inspired by rival Instagram,&#8221; Yeh said.
<p>&#8220;TikTok has grossed $113 million from in-app purchased to date, not including spending on third-party Android app stores such as those in China,&#8221; he added.
<p>The short video sharing app has been downloaded over 1.27 billion times globally, according to Sensor Tower.
<p><em>with inputs from IANS</em>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/tiktok-user-spend-crossed-10-million-last-month/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186249</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software: Recover Your Lost Data</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/salvagedata-data-recovery-software/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/salvagedata-data-recovery-software/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Partner Content]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Internet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=185285</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Salvage Data Featured Iage" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>No matter how careful we are with our data, sometimes tragedies happen and we lose important files. Whether your hard-drive corrupts or your PC had a system-wide failure, losing data can be painful. What&#8217;s even worse is that most data recovery software on the market are quite costly and not all of us can spare [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Salvage Data Featured Iage" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Salvage-Data-Featured-Iage-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>No matter how careful we are with our data, sometimes tragedies happen and we lose important files. Whether your hard-drive corrupts or your PC had a system-wide failure, losing data can be painful. What&#8217;s even worse is that most data recovery software on the market are quite costly and not all of us can spare that kind of money. That&#8217;s why I am so happy to share with you a free data recovery software today. The software that I am talking about is called <a href="https://www.salvagedata.com/software-tools/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software</a>. And in this article, we are going to take a brief look at this software to see what it has to offer us.
<h2>Key Features</h2>
<p>SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software is a really good data recovery software for your Windows, Mac, and Linux machines. We will start by taking a quick look at some of its main features and then move on to its user interface. So, without wasting any more of your time, here are some key features of SALVAGEDATA.
<h3>1. Data Recovery</h3>
<p>Of course, the headlining feature of SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software is its ability to recover lost data. The best part about SALVAGEDATA is that <strong>not only it supports internal hard drives but also external hard drives.</strong> The software is pretty good at finding the deleted files and recovering it. It can recover deleted files, missing partitions, corrupted data, and more. Below are some of the reasons why it&#8217;s so good at recovering data.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185292" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/DATA-REcovery.jpg" alt="DATA REcovery" width="640" height="408" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/DATA-REcovery.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/DATA-REcovery-300x191.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<ul>
<li><strong>Fast and Detailed Scanning</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software <strong>brings a super-fast scanning system</strong> which scans the entire system in just a minute if not a few seconds. Despite bringing a fast scanning system, it is very good at extracting all kinds of lost files. Data scanning is where most data recovery apps fail but SALVAGEDATA is not one of them.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185294" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/1.-Fast-and-Detailed-Scanning.jpg" alt="DATA REcovery" width="640" height="412" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/1.-Fast-and-Detailed-Scanning.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/1.-Fast-and-Detailed-Scanning-300x193.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<ul>
<li><strong>Supports Most File Systems and Formats</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Another big pro of SALVAGEDATA is its<strong> support for a huge range of file systems</strong> and formats. When it comes to file systems, SALVAGEDATA support Windows&#8217; FAT, exFAT, and NTFS file systems along with HFS and HFS+ on macOS, Ext2, Ext3, XFS, and ReiserFS on Linux, and UFS1 and UFS2 on BDS.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185296" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Supported-File-Systems.jpg" alt="Supported File Systems" width="640" height="408" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Supported-File-Systems.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Supported-File-Systems-300x191.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>In all these file systems, SALVAGEDATA supports the recovery of most file types for photos, videos, audio files, documents,emails, and more. Needless to say, there is no popular and even obscure file or file system you are using that cannot be recovered using SALVAGEDATA.</p>
<h3>2. Image and Clone</h3>
<p>Apart from allowing users to recover lost data, SALVAGEDATA <strong>also lets users clone their existing data</strong>. You can easily select the drive that you want to clone and create a clone with just a single click. This feature is great if you want to create a replica of your desktop as a backup.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185298" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Image-and-Clone.jpg" alt="Image and Clone" width="640" height="412" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Image-and-Clone.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Image-and-Clone-300x193.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<h3>3. Secure Wipe</h3>
<p>Finally, there&#8217;s also a &#8220;Secure Wipe&#8221; feature, which as the name suggests,<strong> lets you securely wipe files from your system.</strong> As it&#8217;s clear that SALVAGEDATA and similar apps can let you recover even deleted data, it&#8217;s always good to securely wipe your computer before selling or deprecating it. I use the secure wipe feature quite regularly to complete destroy sensitive files which are not needed anymore. It gives me peace of mind to know that no matter what happens, my sensitive data will never fall in the wrong hands.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185299" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Secure-Wipe.jpg" alt="Secure Wipe" width="640" height="412" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Secure-Wipe.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Secure-Wipe-300x193.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<h2>User Interface and Ease of Use</h2>
<p>SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software is <strong>one of the easiest data recovery apps that I have ever used</strong>. When you launch the app, you are presented with its three main options; Data Recovery, Image and Clone, and Secure Wipe. I have already explained all the three features above. Depending on what you want to do, you will click on any one of the options.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-185301" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/User-Interface.jpg" alt="User Interface" width="640" height="412" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/User-Interface.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/User-Interface-300x193.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>The next steps are pretty simple and similar. You select the drive you want to scan to recover lost data or create a copy or securely wipe and then click on the relevant button at the bottom right of the page. All the buttons and features are clearly visible and you<strong> don&#8217;t have to rifle through menus of items to find what you are looking for.</strong>
<p>Another thing that I would like to mention here is that SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software <strong>shows no ads</strong>. Most free data recovery software rely on ads and they kill the user experience. Since there are no ads on SALVAGEDATA, you are never interrupted or coerced into clicking on something that you are not supposed to. Overall, it gets A+ marks from me as far as UI and usability is concerned.
<h2>Pricing and Availability</h2>
<p>As I told you before, SALVAGEDATA is free to download and use. There are no hidden costs and no ads to kill your user experience. <strong>The app supports all three major desktop operating systems including Windows, macOS, and Linux</strong>. The app is available to download from its website.
<p><em><strong>Check Out SALVAGEDATA Recovery Software:</strong> <a href="https://www.salvagedata.com/software-tools/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a></em>
<h2>Excellent Free Data Recovery Software</h2>
<p>SALVAGEDATA Data Recovery Software is one of the best if not the best free data recovery software that I have used in a while. Not only the app works great but it&#8217;s also easy to use and elegant to look at. This is a software that you should always keep on your computer as you never know when you will need it.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/salvagedata-data-recovery-software/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">185285</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>20 Best Virtual Reality Apps and Experiences You Should Try Right Now</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/best-vr-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/best-vr-apps/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Pranob Mehrotra]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[VR Apps]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=164055</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Best VR Apps" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>Been eyeing a VR headset of late? Already have one but don&#8217;t know which apps to try? Don&#8217;t worry, because we&#8217;ve got you covered. There are a ton of great virtual reality apps and games in the market today and while a lot of them are quite decent, not every one of them is worth [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Best VR Apps" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Best-VR-Apps-featured-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>Been eyeing a VR headset of late? Already have one but don&#8217;t know which apps to try? Don&#8217;t worry, because we&#8217;ve got you covered. There are a ton of great virtual reality apps and games in the market today and while a lot of them are quite decent, not every one of them is worth your time. To save you the trouble of going through poor VR experiences, we&#8217;ve compiled a list of the best VR apps and games you should try right now, with options across a variety of genres so that all of you find something that catches your fancy:
<p><em><strong>Note:</strong> Some of the apps on this list contain flashing lights and images which might trigger seizures, nausea or headaches use them at your own risk. Prices mentioned in the article are for the Android versions of the apps, wherever applicable, pricing on other platforms may vary.</em>
<h2>Best VR Experiences</h2>
<p>For those of you looking for some mind-blowing VR experiences, we&#8217;ve compiled a list of VR based experiences that featuring stunning videos that will transport you to a whole new realm. You can explore different 3D environments right from the comfort of your couch and believe me when I say, some of these experiences are just magical.
<h3>1. Within</h3>
<p>Within is one of the best apps to begin your journey in virtual reality as it offers users a single platform through which they can <strong>discover great VR content from creators around the world</strong>. The app features immersive VR videos spanning across a variety of genres, from <strong>fictional tales to serious documentaries</strong>. The experimental section on the app is home to some fun, trippy videos which will transport you to another dimension. If you&#8217;re someone who enjoys great video content, then I&#8217;m pretty sure you&#8217;ll find yourself spending increasing amounts of time on Within. It&#8217;s definitely one of the best VR experiences out there.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168071" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/within-app-screenshot.jpg" alt="Within app screenshot" width="640" height="408" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/within-app-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/within-app-screenshot-300x191.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream), iOS, Windows, Oculus, PlayStation VR, HTC Vive</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download Within (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shakingearthdigital.vrsecardboard&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>2. BBC Earth: Life in VR</h3>
<p>If you&#8217;re looking for something a bit more informative, one of the best VR apps you should definitely check out is BBC Earth: Life in VR. It&#8217;s a <strong>Google Play Award winning app</strong> that allows users to <strong>experience the natural world in VR</strong>. The cartoonish animation makes the app <strong>perfect for young kids</strong> who can use it to learn a lot about life around them. The app focuses on the fauna round the Californian coast, <strong>delving to a microscopic level to help you discover organisms</strong> that you&#8217;ve never seen before and it even allows you to dive deep into the ocean alongside a Sperm Whale to get closer to the gargantuan creature than you&#8217;ve ever been before.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-168074 size-full" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/bbc-earth-vr-app-screenshot.jpg" alt="BBC earth screenshot" width="640" height="406" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/bbc-earth-vr-app-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/bbc-earth-vr-app-screenshot-300x190.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Daydream exclusive</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download BBC Earth: Life in VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bbc.lifeinvr01" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>3. InCell VR</h3>
<p>One of the<strong> best virtual reality apps for educational purposes</strong> &#8211; InCell VR &#8211; has been designed to teach you how the human body works by <strong>taking you down to the cellular level and helping you understand just what goes on inside the building blocks of our body</strong>. In order to make the experience a bit more interesting for you, the app gamifies the biology with <strong>an action/racing game thrown into the mix</strong>. The stunning visuals, along with the gaming aspect of the app, really go a long way in ensuring that you learn some interesting things about cells and their components.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168076" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/incell-vr-screenshot.jpg" alt="incell vr screenshot" width="640" height="472" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/incell-vr-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/incell-vr-screenshot-300x221.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/incell-vr-screenshot-80x60.jpg 80w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/incell-vr-screenshot-569x420.jpg 569w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Cardboard/Daydream, iOS, Samsung Gear VR, Windows, HTC Vive, Oculus</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download InCell VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nivalvr.incell&amp;hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em></p>
<h3>4. Horizons</h3>
<p>Not really into all the educational content? Then you should probably try Horizons, a visual masterpiece which takes you an a series of <strong>interactive journeys based on the music of renowned producer Bonobo</strong>. The app allows you to control the music, and the music, in turn, controls the virtual world in front of your eyes. The <strong>psychedelic experience</strong> is definitely worth checking out and I&#8217;m sure that the visuals, combined with the spatial sound, will amaze you. If you&#8217;re a fan of Bonobo&#8217;s work, then you shouldn&#8217;t think twice before downloading this app.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168078" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/horizons-screenshot.jpg" alt="horizons screenshots" width="640" height="395" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/horizons-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/horizons-screenshot-300x185.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/horizons-screenshot-356x220.jpg 356w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Daydream</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download Horizons (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.reactify.HorizonsVR" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>5. Star Chart</h3>
<p>Take off from Earth and explore the solar system and the wide expanse of space beyond with Star Chart VR &#8211; <strong>a real-time space simulation</strong> which gives you accurate locations of the celestial bodies you can see from Earth. Get up close to the Sun or drift far away to the cold, deep space around Pluto; count Saturn&#8217;s rings or view thousands of the most visible stars in the night sky; you can do it all with Star Chart. It&#8217;s definitely one of the best immersive apps I&#8217;ve tried till date and I especially like the part where the app <strong>allows you to experience the most memorable moments of human space exploration</strong>, something you might have just seen on TV or YouTube up until now.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168079" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/star-chart-screenshot.jpg" alt="star chart screenshot" width="640" height="360" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/star-chart-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/star-chart-screenshot-300x169.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream/Google Cardboard), Windows, iOS, macOS, Xbox 360, Oculus</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> $4.99</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Download Star Chart (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.escapistgames.starchartvr.daydream&amp;hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$4.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>6. VR Media and Movie Apps &#8211; Netflix VR / YouTube VR / Hulu VR</h3>
<p>If you love watching movies you will certainly appreciate these VR apps which allow you to experience your favorite movies in a virtual environment. <strong>There are main popular media streaming services which bring their virtual reality apps</strong> to give you the best movie-watching experience. Some of the prominent streaming services which support VR experience include Netflix, YouTube, Hulu, sling TV, Plex VR, and more.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186232" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Hulu-VR.jpg" alt="Hulu VR" width="640" height="330" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Hulu-VR.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Hulu-VR-300x155.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>My favorite media streaming VR apps are <a href="https://beebom.com/how-use-netflix-vr-google-daydream-platform/" >Netflix VR</a> and YouTube VR as thats where I spent most of my time on. You can find these VR apps by simply searching for them in the Google Play Store or Apple App Store. <strong>Some of these apps also support Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, and other VR platforms.</strong> Lastly, while these apps are free to download and use, you will need to have a paid account with the service (where it is required) to stream media.
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Cardboard, Google Daydream, HTC Vive, Oculus Rift and more.</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> None of the streaming service charge extra for VR</em>
<p><em><strong>Download:</strong> Netflix VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.netflix.android_vr&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">free</a>), YouTube VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.youtube.vr&amp;hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">free</a>), Hulu VR (<a href="https://help.hulu.com/s/article/guide-to-hulu-virtual-reality?language=en_US" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">free</a>), Sling TV VR (<a href="https://www.oculus.com/experiences/go/2412412708773095/?locale=en_US" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">free</a>), Plex VR (<a href="https://www.plex.tv/your-media/virtual-reality/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">free</a>)</em>
<h3>7. Dream Vision VR Apps</h3>
<p>Dream Vision is a company which makes a ton of VR apps and games.<strong> Made by Tzumi Electronics, Dream Vision VR aims to enhance</strong> your augmented and virtual reality universe with a collection of the best VR apps, videos, and image content available. Under the brand name Dream360, the company has released tons of VR and AR apps.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186233" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Dream-Vision-VR-Apps.jpg" alt="Dream Vision VR Apps" width="640" height="307" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Dream-Vision-VR-Apps.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Dream-Vision-VR-Apps-300x144.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></p>
<p>Some of the <strong>famous Dream360 VR apps include Romans From Mars 360, VR Flight Simulator, VR Noir, VR Horror World</strong>, VR Hungry Shark Cage, Inception: VR &amp; 360 Videos, and more. The first VR app on this list &#8220;Within&#8221; is also made by Dream Vision apps. All these apps are available for both iOS and Android platforms and you can check them all out by clicking on the link below.
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android and iOS</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download:</strong> <a href="http://dream360.com/apps/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a></em>
<h3>8. NYT VR</h3>
<p>Developed by New York Times, <strong>NYT VR takes you up and close to riveting stories captured by the publications journalists</strong>. If you&#8217;re looking to stay connected and up to date with everything that&#8217;s happening around the world, but don&#8217;t just want to read news to get that information, then you should definitely try out NYT VR. The app <strong>has some amazing content on offer</strong> and due to the fact that it immerses you and takes you to ground zero, the experience and the information that you gain about a particular topic are unmatched. Quick tip, download the videos before you play them or you might encounter a black screen if your internet connection isn&#8217;t stable.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168080" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/nyt-vr-screenshot.jpg" alt="nyt vr screenshot" width="640" height="349" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/nyt-vr-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/nyt-vr-screenshot-300x164.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream/Google Cardboard), iOS, Samsung Gear VR</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download NYT VR (<a href="http://www.nytimes.com/marketing/nytvr/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em></p>
<h3>9. Fulldive VR</h3>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-164058 size-full" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Fulldive-VR.jpg" alt="Fulldive VR screenshot" width="640" height="378" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Fulldive-VR.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Fulldive-VR-300x177.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>Fulldive VR is sort of <strong>a social media app for virtual reality</strong> which hosts 100 percent user generated content that you can watch on your VR headset. Being a social platform, the app allows you to <strong>add friends from around the world</strong> and experience their content. You can even share VR content that you created on the platform and you can rest assured that it will reach VR enthusiasts worldwide. Other social features include <strong>reactions, comments and sharing</strong>, which means that the VR content that you upload on the app sure has a strong chance of going viral. You can even discover other great VR apps and games on the Fulldive, which is an added bonus.<br />
<span id="vrapps"></span>
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream/Google Cardboard), iOS</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download Fulldive VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=in.fulldive.shell" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h2>Best VR Games</h2>
<p>In case you&#8217;re more interested in an interactive experience, however, you should definitely check out the following VR apps and games. These 3D apps and games provide an interactive experience like no other, with some even giving you the opportunity to play with friends even when you have a single VR headset between you. We have included the best apps and games that offer an immersive experience here and I&#8217;m sure you&#8217;ll find something great that will help you make good use of your VR headset.
<h3>1. Mekorama VR</h3>
<p>Mekorama is a fairly popular <strong>puzzle game</strong> and has featured on many of our <a href="https://beebom.com/low-mb-games-android/" >best Android games</a> lists, so when I found out that there was a VR version as well, I didn&#8217;t think twice before getting it on my phone. For those who haven&#8217;t played Mekorama before, it&#8217;s a three dimensional puzzle game in which you have to control a cute robot and take him from point A to point B, overcoming tricky obstacles all along the way. The VR version of Mekorama really does justice to the 3D puzzle as it <strong>allows you to view the diorama from any angle </strong>in full virtual reality. It looks really beautiful, and controlling the robot in VR is just a really fun experience, but unfortunately there&#8217;s no multiplayer angle to the game. If puzzle games are your jam, Mekorama VR is definitely one of the best VR apps you&#8217;ll find right now. However, the game is only available for Google&#8217;s Daydream platform, so unless you have a Daydream ready phone, and a Daydream headset, you&#8217;ll not be able to play it.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168082" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/mekorama-vr-screenshot.jpg" alt="mekorama vr screenshot" width="640" height="389" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/mekorama-vr-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/mekorama-vr-screenshot-300x182.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Daydream</p>
<p><strong>Price:</strong> $3.99
<p><em><strong>Download Mekorama VR (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.martinmagni.mekorama.vr&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$3.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>2. Keep Talking &amp; Nobody Explodes</h3>
<p>One of the best VR games I&#8217;ve tried in a while is &#8220;Keep Talking and Nobody Explodes.&#8221; In case you&#8217;re hanging out with a bunch of friends, but have just a single VR headset between you guys, then you should definitely try out Keep Talking &amp; Nobody Explodes &#8211; an <strong>engaging puzzle game</strong> in which you and your friends have to think fast or all of you risk blowing up. The game&#8217;s premise is quite simple to understand, with <strong>one player trapped in a virtual room with a ticking time bomb</strong>, and the others giving instructions on how they can diffuse the bomb. However, the game in itself is quite tricky as each new bomb is unique and the bomb defusal manual doesn&#8217;t really give you the easiest directions. Try it out at your next get together, I&#8217;m sure you&#8217;ll have a ton of fun.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168084" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes-screenshot.jpg" alt="keep talking and nobody explodes screenshot" width="640" height="380" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/keep-talking-and-nobody-explodes-screenshot-300x178.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream), iOS, Xbox One, PlayStation 4, Windows, macOS, Linux, Oculus, HTC Vive
<p><strong>Price:</strong> $9.99
<p><em><strong>Download Keep Talking &amp; Nobody Explodes (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.steelcrategames.keeptalkingandnobodyexplodes" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$9.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>3. Thumper</h3>
<p>Do music based games catch your fancy? Then you should consider trying out Thumper &#8211; a rhythm based action game in which you play as a space beetle, running down an <strong>endless psychedelic track</strong>, trying its best to confront the maniacal giant head from the future. Thumper offers <strong>nine different levels</strong> of rhythm hell with <strong>epic boss battles, simple controls</strong>, along with visuals and sounds that will definitely give you a sensory overload. It goes without saying that people who&#8217;re susceptible to seizures should stay away from this game as it&#8217;s full of flashing lights and images.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168085" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/thumper-screenshot.jpg" alt="thumper screenshot" width="640" height="414" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/thumper-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/thumper-screenshot-300x194.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></p>
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> iOS, Windows, Oculus, HTC Vive
<p><strong>Price:</strong> $19.99
<p><em><strong>Download Thumper (<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/356400/Thumper/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$19.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>4. Virtual Virtual Reality</h3>
<p>Another great VR game that has been honored by a <strong>Google Play Award for the best VR experience</strong> &#8211; Virtual Virtual Reality &#8211; is also a must try for all of you VR fans out there. As the name suggests, Virtual Virtual Reality <strong>puts you in a virtual world</strong> where you start as a new worker for Activitude &#8211; a sci-fi facility that provides services to AI clients. But that&#8217;s not all, there are multiple virtual worlds within this virtual world in which there are a number of mini games that you can play. I won&#8217;t spoil the fun for you by giving you all of the details, you really need to try the game to truly experience virtual virtual reality or just too much virtual reality.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168086" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/virtual-virtual-reality-screenshot.jpg" alt="virtual virtual reality screenshot" width="640" height="419" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/virtual-virtual-reality-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/virtual-virtual-reality-screenshot-300x196.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Daydream
<p><strong>Price:</strong> $8.99
<p><em><strong>Download Virtual Virtual Reality (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.TenderClaws.VVR" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$8.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>5. Deep Space Battle</h3>
<p>Looking for something a bit more simple? Perhaps you should give Deep Space Battle a shot. A fun VR game in which you <strong>control a spaceship deep in space</strong> and <strong>defend against the invasion of the Shadow Fleet</strong>. It does sound quite easy, but the game can be really challenging to play as you have to <strong>control the movements of the ship with your head</strong>. You have a variety of ships you can choose from to take down the Shadow Fleet and the best part is that everything is completely free, without any ads. Try out Deep Space Battle if you&#8217;re looking for a casual and immersive game that you can play whenever you&#8217;ve got a couple of minutes to kill.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168087" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/deep-space-battle.jpg" alt="deep space battle screenshot" width="640" height="367" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/deep-space-battle.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/deep-space-battle-300x172.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Google Cardboard
<p><strong>Price:</strong> Free
<p><em><strong>Download Deep Space Battle (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gamearx.spacerumble" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>6. Rez Infinite</h3>
<p>Another VR game that you should definitely try, Rez Infinite is an <strong>action packed shooter with incredible environments</strong> that you, as a hacker, have to traverse. The game has an otherworldly premise in which you have to <strong>travel through cyberspace</strong> filled with firewalls, viruses and other obstacles to jumpstart an AI called Eden that has fallen into a vegetative state. Eden is the core of Project-K, a system designed to curb the rising crime rates in the real world. So your failure to reach Eden and get it back up and running will have some serious consequences.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168088" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/rez-infinite-screenshot.jpg" alt="rez infinite screenshot" width="640" height="392" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/rez-infinite-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/rez-infinite-screenshot-300x184.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream), PlayStation VR, Oculus, HTC Vive, Windows
<p><strong>Price:</strong> Free with in-game purchases
<p><em><strong>Download Rez Infinite (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.enhancegames.rez&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free, with in-app purchases</a>)</strong></em></p>
<h3>7. Eclipse: Edge of Light</h3>
<p><strong>Explore an alien landscape with Eclipse: Edge of Light</strong>, a VR adventure game in which you&#8217;re crash landed on an alien planet armed with a powerful relic &#8211; the Artifact &#8211; that helps you <strong>interact with ancient technology and gives you superpowers</strong>. Eclipse: Edge of Light has some immersive visuals that will surely blow you away. On top of that, the game <strong>makes excellent use of the Daydream controller</strong> which really enhances the gameplay aspect of it, you can move around, interact with objects and complete puzzles to progress the storyline.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168089" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/eclipse-edge-of-light-screenshot.jpg" alt="eclipse edge of light screenshot" width="640" height="378" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/eclipse-edge-of-light-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/eclipse-edge-of-light-screenshot-300x177.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream), Oculus, Samsung Gear VR
<p><strong>Price:</strong> $8.99
<p><em><strong>Download Eclipse: Edge of Light (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.WhiteElkLLC.EclipseEdgeOfLight&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$8.99</a>)</strong></em>
<h3>8. Twilight Pioneers</h3>
<p>Have you ever wondered if you would experience a <strong>full-scale RPG in VR</strong>? Well, you can with Twilight Pioneers &#8211; a <strong>first-person action RPG based in a fantasy world full of magic</strong>. The game offers an immersive VR experience, making good use of the Daydream controller to give free movement to the players. You can <strong>wield a variety of different weapons</strong> and embark on a <strong>thrilling quest filled with exploration, skirmishes and epic boss battles</strong>. It&#8217;s like playing World of Warcraft in first-person. Now, I&#8217;m sure some of you are going to love that.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-168090" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/twilight-pioneers-screenshot.jpg" alt="twilight pioneers screenshot" width="640" height="395" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/twilight-pioneers-screenshot.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/twilight-pioneers-screenshot-300x185.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/twilight-pioneers-screenshot-356x220.jpg 356w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream)
<p><strong>Price:</strong> Free</p>
<p><em><strong>Download Twilight Pioneers (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.netease.vr&amp;hl=en" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Free</a>)</strong></em>
<h3><strong>Horror and Scary VR Games</strong></h3>
<p>One of the most popular VR games genres is Horror. If you are one of those Gamers who like to experience bone-chilling adventure, you must play these scary horror VR games.
<h3>9. The Exorcist: Legion VR</h3>
<p>If you are someone who considers themselves bold, fearless, and daring then you should play this game and find out how nerveless you really are. <strong>Created by the horror maestro William Peter Blatty and based on the academy-award winning world,</strong> &#8220;The Exorcist: Legion VR&#8221; will test your mental strength to its extreme. The game is chapterized where each chapter features a new demonic entity which will test your courage.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186235" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Chapter-1-First-Rites.jpg" alt="Chapter 1 First Rites" width="640" height="343" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Chapter-1-First-Rites.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Chapter-1-First-Rites-300x161.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>This game without a doubt delivers one of the best if not the best horror experiences you will ever have.<strong> The graphics are scary, the music is ominous, and the demons are well, demonic as hell.</strong> The game is available for HTC Vive and Oculus Rift only, so keep that in mind. Finally, this game is not for light-hearted people so if you scare easily, be warned!
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> HTC Vive and Oculus Rift</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> $4.99 for Chapter 1</em>
<p><em><strong>Download The Exorcist: Legion VR &#8211; Chapter 1</strong> (<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/708580/The_Exorcist_Legion_VR__Chapter_1_First_Rites/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">$4.99</a>)</em>
<h3>10. House of Terror: Valerie’s Revenge (VR)</h3>
<p>House of Terror: Valerie&#8217;s Revenge is a Virtual Reality game in which gamers have to<strong> search through dark environments full of traps and monsters</strong>. In the game, you will have to solve puzzles, collect clues, and solve the riddles to advance. You will have to do this while keeping away from the monsters and ghouls so that you are not caught.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186236" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/House-of-Terror.jpg" alt="House of Terror" width="640" height="403" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/House-of-Terror.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/House-of-Terror-300x189.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>The <strong>ominous music combined with dark environments full of jump scares</strong> will surely get on your nerves. If you love horror games, then there is no better way to experience them in VR. Do note that you will need Bluetooth joysticks to play this game. One thing that I love about this game is that it is compatible with Google Cardboard which means you don&#8217;t have to buy a costly VR headset to play it.
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream/Google Cardboard), iOS</em>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free</em>
<p><em><strong>Download House of Terror: Valerie&#8217;s Revenge</strong> (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.BloompixStudios.HouseOfTerrorVRFree&amp;hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Android</a> / <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/house-of-terror-vr/id946382493" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">iOS</a>)</em>
<h3>11. Sisters</h3>
<p>Another great VR horror game is the &#8220;Sisters&#8221; which will always keep you one the edge of your proverbial seat. <strong>Sisters is a VR ghost story in which you will have to spend a night alone in the house</strong> to find out what happened to yout aunt. The night is long and full of terrors and you will discover that you are not so alone after all. Be careful as there&#8217;s something in the house that doesn&#8217;t want you there.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186237" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Sisters.jpg" alt="Sisters" width="640" height="348" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Sisters.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Sisters-300x163.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>The game has been <strong>designed specifically for mobile VR experience and works with Google Cardboard and other VR headsets</strong>. It features head tracking as it allows you to look around in the 360-degree scary digitally painted environment. The environment is also interactive that means it will respond to what you are looking at. Sisters might not be in the list of best VR games out there, however, if you are looking for a scary VR adventure, it will serve the purpose just fine.
<p><em><strong>Supported platforms:</strong> Android (Google Daydream/Google Cardboard), iOS</em></p>
<p><em><strong>Price:</strong> Free, in-app purchases</em>
<p><em><strong>Download Sisters</strong> (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.otherworld.Sisters&amp;hl=en_IN" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Android</a> / <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sisters-a-vr-ghost-story/id957212695" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">iOS</a>)</em>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>SEE ALSO: </strong><a href="https://beebom.com/best-psvr-games/"><strong>15 Best PlayStation VR Games You Should Be Playing</strong></a>
<h2>Check Out The Best VR Apps and Enjoy Your VR Headset</h2>
<p>Did any of these aforementioned experiences and immersive apps grab your attention? Have you tried any other VR app that you think should be included on this list? Do let us know in the comments section below. And if, in case, you try out one of the listed experiences, make sure you share which experience you liked the most. In my time testing out these apps, I really liked the Tokyo Light Odyssey and La Fuga videos in the experimental section on Within, you should definitely check those out on your VR headset.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/best-vr-apps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">164055</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xiaomi May Ditch &#8216;Poco&#8217; Brand Following Redmi K20 Launch, Says Analyst</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/xiaomi-ditch-poco-redmi-k20-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/xiaomi-ditch-poco-redmi-k20-launch/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kishalaya Kundu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poco F1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poco F2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xiaomi]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186215</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>Adding more fuel to persistent speculations about the fate of the &#8216;Poco&#8217; brand from Xiaomi, an IDC analyst has now claimed that the company may be planning to scrap the value brand for good. The assertion from IDC research director, Navkendar Singh, comes just days after POCO general manager, Jai Mani, called it quits following [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/Poco-f1-miui-630x420.jpg 630w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>Adding more fuel to persistent speculations about the fate of the <em>&#8216;Poco&#8217;</em> brand from Xiaomi, an IDC analyst has now claimed that the company may be planning to scrap the value brand for good. The assertion from IDC research director, Navkendar Singh, comes just days after POCO general manager, <a href="https://beebom.com/poco-head-and-xiaomis-global-spokesperson-leave-company/" >Jai Mani, called it quits</a> following the <a href="https://beebom.com/redmi-k20-pro-launched-india-price-specs-availability/" >launch of the Redmi K20 and K20 Pro</a> in India last week.
<p>Speaking to ET, Singh said he believes that there&#8217;s just no space in the market for the Poco brand now that its positioning has been usurped by the K20 series. According to him: <em>&#8220;Poco was launched to give high-end chosen few specs at mid-range prices, with clear compromises on design language &#8230; But now, with this aggressive pricing of K series by Xiaomi with its absolute flagship specs, hardware, and design, the reason for the existence of Poco as a brand is in doubt&#8221;</em>.
<p>Xiaomi, however, continues to officially deny that Poco has hit the end of the road. In an official statement to ET, a company spokesperson said: <em>&#8220;For Poco, nothing changes because of an executive leaving and work will go on as planned&#8221;</em>. Xiaomi&#8217;s India head, Manu Kumar Jain, however, didn&#8217;t deny anything outright, saying: <em>&#8220;We will not be able to answer it (the question about Poco&#8217;s future) right now&#8221;</em>.
<p>In case you don&#8217;t know it already, the former head of Poco, Jai Mani, unceremoniously left Xiaomi after five years last week. He was hired by former Xiaomi global VP, Hugo Barra, and had played a major role in the launch of the <a href="https://beebom.com/xiaomi-poco-f1-review/" >Poco F1</a> last year. While the device went on to become a massive hit in India, it received mixed response elsewhere around the world.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/xiaomi-ditch-poco-redmi-k20-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186215</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Honor Band 5 Launched With Blood Oxygen Monitor, Heart Rate Tracker and More</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/honor-band-5-launched-specs-pricing-availability/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/honor-band-5-launched-specs-pricing-availability/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Kishalaya Kundu]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Honor Band 5]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186182</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p>At its press event earlier today, Huawei launched its Honor Band 5 fitness tracker alongside the Honor 9X lineup and the MateBook Pro laptop. A successor to the Honor Band 4 that was launched last year in China and earlier this year in India, the device is expected to give tough competition to the Mi [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="750" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website.jpg 750w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-696x464.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-630x420.jpg 630w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-website-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 750px) 100vw, 750px" /></p><p>At its press event earlier today, Huawei launched its Honor Band 5 fitness tracker alongside the Honor 9X lineup and the MateBook Pro laptop. A successor to the <a href="https://beebom.com/honor-band-4-india-launch/" >Honor Band 4</a> that was launched last year in China and earlier this year in India, the device is expected to give tough competition to the Mi Band 4 that was <a href="https://beebom.com/mi-band-4-launched/" >launched last month</a> in China and reportedly <a href="https://beebom.com/mi-band-4-global-shipments-1-million-8-days/" >shipped one million units</a> globally within just 8 days.
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-186212" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-body.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="370" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-body.jpg 640w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/Honor-Band-5-body-300x173.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" />
<p>As was amply evident from <a href="https://beebom.com/honor-band-5-officially-teased/" >the official teasers</a>, the design of the new device is more of an evolution over its predecessor, with the color AMOLED display and the circular button below it. The device features a 0.95-inch AMOLED screen (240 x 120 pixel resolution) with 2.5D curved glass. The top-end Chinese model also comes with an NFC chip, but it isn&#8217;t immediately clear as to whether it will make it to global markets.
<p>As was earlier confirmed by Honor CEO, George Zhao, the fitness tracker comes with a blood oxygen monitor. It can also detect hypoxemia dizziness, which is a condition that stems from the body not getting the amount of oxygen it needs for normal functioning. One of the other highlights of the new device is its 24-hour heart rate monitoring with an AI algorithm that the company claims has an accuracy of 97.8 percent. It can also track sleep patterns with Huawei TruSleep 2.0.
<p>The Honor Band 5 supports Bluetooth 4.2 and is waterproof up to a depth of 50 meters. It is also compatible with Android 4.4 KitKat and above, as well as iOS 9 and later. The device also carries a 100mAh battery that the company claims is good enough to last up to 14 days with the real-time heart-rate monitoring turned off. With the feature turned on, the battery will still last up to 6 days, the company said.
<p>The Honor Band 5 has been priced starting at 189 yuan (around Rs. 1,900), while the NFC version comes with a 219 yuan (around Rs. 2,200) price-tag. They&#8217;ll go on sale in China starting July 29. There&#8217;s no immediate word on when the device will be launched internationally, including in India, but we&#8217;ll definitely get to know more in the days ahead.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/honor-band-5-launched-specs-pricing-availability/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186182</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nubia Red Magic 3S Will Also Come with the Snapdragon 855 Plus</title>
		<link>https://beebom.com/nubia-red-magic-3s-snapdragon-855-plus-rumoured/</link>
		<comments>https://beebom.com/nubia-red-magic-3s-snapdragon-855-plus-rumoured/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Akshay Gangwar]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming Phone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nubia Red Magic 3S]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snapdragon 855 Plus]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://beebom.com/?p=186221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p><img width="751" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras.jpg 751w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-696x463.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-631x420.jpg 631w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /></p>After Qualcomm announced the new Snapdragon 855 Plus with increased CPU and GPU clock speeds, companies jumped at the chance to bring phones out with the new flagship processor. Asus announced that the ROG Phone 2 will come with the Snapdragon 855 Plus, Xiaomi is expected to launch the Black Shark 2 with a Snapdragon [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img width="751" height="500" src="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras.jpg 751w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-300x200.jpg 300w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-696x463.jpg 696w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-631x420.jpg 631w, https://beebom.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/nubia-red-magic-3-cameras-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /></p><p>After Qualcomm <a href="https://beebom.com/snapdragon-855-plus-announced/" >announced the new Snapdragon 855 Plus</a> with increased CPU and GPU clock speeds, companies jumped at the chance to bring phones out with the new flagship processor. Asus announced that the <a href="https://beebom.com/rog-phone-2-official-specs-features/" >ROG Phone 2</a> will <a href="https://beebom.com/rog-phone-2-snapdragon-855-plus/" >come with the Snapdragon 855 Plus</a>, Xiaomi is expected to launch the <a href="https://beebom.com/black-shark-2-pro-launch-july-30/" >Black Shark 2 with a Snapdragon 855 Plus</a> on July 30, a <a href="https://beebom.com/redmi-phone-snapdragon-855-plus-confirmed/" >Redmi phone with Snapdragon 855 Plus</a> was recently confirmed, and rumors are suggesting that the <a href="https://beebom.com/pixel-4-xl-specs-leaked-6gb-ram-snapdragon-855-plus-more/" >Pixel 4 and 4 XL will also come with the Snapdragon 855 Plus</a>.
<p>Well, joining the ranks of these smartphones that have been confirmed or are rumoured to pack in the Snapdragon 855 Plus, Nubia is expected to put the latest flagship processor in its upcoming gaming phone too — the Nubia Red Magic 3S.
<p>This isn&#8217;t confirmed yet, but comes from industry insider Sudhanshu Ambhore, who tweeted that Nubia&#8217;s upcoming Red Magic 3S will come with the Snapdragon 855 Plus.
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The upcoming Snapdragon 855 Plus phone from Nubia is the Nubia Red Magic 3S. <a href="https://t.co/Ee0vVZc6NQ" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Ee0vVZc6NQ</a>
<p>&mdash; Sudhanshu Ambhore (@Sudhanshu1414) <a href="https://twitter.com/Sudhanshu1414/status/1153162045774151681?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">July 22, 2019</a></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
<p>The Snapdragon 855 Plus doesn&#8217;t change a whole lot in terms of hardware, but overclocks the Kryo 485 cores in the processor to a whopping 2.96GHz, while the Adreno 640 is claimed to be clocked 15% higher than the 640 in the regular Snapdragon 855.
<p>Meanwhile, the Red Magic 3S is shrouded in mystery, with no details about the phone being available so far, other than this Snapdragon 855 Plus rumour. Still, since it&#8217;s a gaming phone, it should come with 8 to 12GB of RAM, and 256 to 512GB onboard storage, along with some exciting gaming centric features.
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://beebom.com/nubia-red-magic-3s-snapdragon-855-plus-rumoured/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
	<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">186221</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
